{
    "subject": "resource/Edward_Garnier",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Wuppertal",
    "human_readable": "Edward Garnier was born in Wuppertal.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9131154417991638,
            "question": "Was Wuppertal a significant place for Edward Garnier?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.850426971912384,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Edward Garnier and Wuppertal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.845594584941864,
            "question": "Where was Edward Garnier born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7615064382553101,
            "question": "In what country was Edward Garnier born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5260788202285767,
            "question": "What is the significance of being born in Wuppertal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48512011766433716,
            "question": "What is Edward Garnier known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46755993366241455,
            "question": "Can you tell me about other famous people born in Wuppertal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4314712882041931,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of a person born in Wuppertal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41906803846359253,
            "question": "Is Edward Garnier from Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28975874185562134,
            "question": "Do you know anything else about Edward Garnier's life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edward Garnier was born in Wuppertal.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2654_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Edward Garnier from Germany?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2654_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics of a person born in Wuppertal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2654_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about other famous people born in Wuppertal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2654_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2654_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2654_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2654_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2654_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2654_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2654_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2654_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2654_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2654_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2654_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Edward Garnier was born on October 26, 1952, in Wuppertal, North Rhine-Westphalia, Germany. Therefore, the statement that Edward Garnier was born in Wuppertal is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}